{
    "subject": "resource/Hot_Rod_Circuit",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Auburn,_Alabama",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Hot Rod Circuit is Auburn, Alabama.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8652159571647644,
            "question": "In which state is Hot Rod Circuit's hometown located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8348782658576965,
            "question": "Which band's hometown is Auburn, Alabama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6983540654182434,
            "question": "Auburn, Alabama is known as the hometown of what musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6377330422401428,
            "question": "Where is Hot Rod Circuit from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6214063763618469,
            "question": "What city is associated with Hot Rod Circuit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5201489925384521,
            "question": "Where did Hot Rod Circuit originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4257814288139343,
            "question": "Is Hot Rod Circuit originally from a city in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37707120180130005,
            "question": "What musical group is based in Auburn, Alabama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2791377604007721,
            "question": "What band hails from Auburn, Alabama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20701469480991364,
            "question": "Can you name a band with roots in Auburn, Alabama?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Hot Rod Circuit is Auburn, Alabama.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3708_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What band hails from Auburn, Alabama?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3708_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical group is based in Auburn, Alabama?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3708_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Hot Rod Circuit originally from a city in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3708_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3708_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple \"Pat Frank author Alas, Babylon\" has an output value of yes because the information in the document does not contradict this statement.\n\nThe triple \"Elisabeth Domitien office Iraq\" has an output value of no because Elisabeth Domitien was a politician from the Democratic Republic of Congo and served as Prime Minister of the country from 1998 to 2001, according to the documents. \n\nHowever, The question about Hot Rod Circuit is different since it is asking for factual information directly present in the context.\n\nThe correct response is:\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Hot Rod Circuit were an indie rock/rock band from Auburn, Alabama established in 1999,\" which supports the statement that the hometown of Hot Rod Circuit is Auburn, Alabama."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}